Hrushka Daria

A full-time Product Manager with over 5 years in the IT industry. Specializing in product management, software development, and business analysis. Possesses a unique blend of technical expertise and leadership, with a strong focus on collaboration, problem-solving, and driving continuous improvement.

Previously, I was a Dev Team Lead, blending management with hands-on development tasks.

+38 (066) 801-47-53

telegram: <u>@kldasha</u> daria.hrushka@gmail.com

website: portfolio

EXPERIENCE

<u>Interkassa</u>. Payment systems aggregator — *BA to product manager* Kyiv, Ukraine

JULY 2022 - NOWADAYS

Since assuming the role of Product Manager, led the team to a 50% increase in feature development output. Successfully created a comprehensive backlog, outlining strategic improvements for the upcoming year. My role encompassed:

- Product Roadmap: formed and monitored product roadmaps, aligning with market needs and business priorities.
- **Requirements Engineering:** formed detailed product requirements, ensuring they captured the essence of user needs and business goals.
- **Agile**: lead and facilitate daily scrums, sprint planning, sprint reviews, and retrospectives
- **Technical Collaboration**: partnered closely with engineering teams, communicating about product vision, and priorities, clarifying tasks, creating spikes, monitoring and managing their implementation.
- System Architecture: contributed to the system architecture design, ensuring scalability and alignment with product goals.
- Performance Metrics: established and monitored key performance indicators to ensure product effectiveness.
- **Customer Engagement:** gathered feedback to inform product development and enhance customer satisfaction.
- **Documentation Leadership**: created an internal wiki, standardizing terminology and improving cross-departmental communication.
- Developed and maintained an external documentation solution (<u>Interkassa wiki website</u>), managing all aspects from page styling to code optimization.
- Business Analysis: analyzed complex datasets to identify opportunities and drive performance enhancements.
- Continuously proposed innovative solutions for improved business interaction, such as external tutorials, online merchant integration documentation, etc.

<u>Fidesint</u>. Integration consultancy — *integration developer* Kyiv, Ukraine

SEPTEMBER 2021 – JULY 2022

In addition to software development, my tasks included full project lifecycle management:

- Solely responsible for the complete project lifecycle, from gathering requirements to ensuring timely delivery.
- Created intermediate documentation and clear presentations for better communication with the customer, clarification of product requirements, and progress control.
- Managed client communication, project documentation, and

LANGUAGES

English: professional proficiency Ukrainian: native speaker Russian: native speaker Turkish: beginner

SKILLS

Cross-functional team leadership,
Product Road mapping, Agile,
Scrum, Strategic planning, Product
development, Product design,
Communication, Problem-solving,
Decision-making, Business
Analysis, Jira, Confluence, Kibana,
Grafana, Sentry, Google Cloud,
Draw Io, Lighthouse, Git, Bitbucket,
Figma, Postman

CERTIFICATES

Pro Project Management: 2023 PMP Certification Prep Course: 2023 Complete business analysis course:

2022

Technical writing: 2022

- coordinated the development process.
- Ensured alignment between development, stakeholders, and customer needs.
- Organized workflows and processes, ensuring optimal project execution.
- Development of schemes and diagrams to illustrate the operation of the software product.
- Structured large volumes of information.

Ad Viser. Financial company — lead front-end developer, team lead Kyiv, Ukraine

SEPTEMBER 2020 - OCTOBER 2021

Project Leadership & Planning:

- Oversaw planning, development, and full delivery process of multiple projects.
- Managed a small team of developers, providing mentorship and ensuring alignment with project goals.
- Developed and maintained a custom framework, streamlining application development.
- Facilitated clear communication and documentation between teams and stakeholders.

<u>Aweb Systems</u>. Marketing company — *front-end developer* Kyiv, Ukraine

JULY 2019 - FEBRUARY 2020

Software Development & Collaboration:

- Collaborated on front-end development projects, focusing on efficient and quality delivery.
- Assisted in creating documentation and communication materials, supporting overall project success.

ARTICLES

The construction of cospectral graphs related to the generalized adjacency matrix;

"Cospectral graphs and the generalized adjacency matrix" for the <u>KPI scientific conference</u>;

"Keypoint SIFT descriptors" for the international scientific conference "Semiconductor materials, IT and photovoltaics";

"Using SIFT (Scale Invariant Feature Transform) descriptors for mapping template and image" for the "IT perspective" magazine.

PM SKILLS

- **Project Coordination**: Proven ability in managing multifaceted projects, team collaboration, and strategic improvements.
- Technical Expertise: Extensive skills across various tools and languages.
- **Technical Communication**: Exceptional skills in technical communication, both in writing and speaking, with the ability to convey complex concepts clearly and effectively.
- **People Skills**: Strong interpersonal skills, enabling effortless communication with various stakeholders. Possesses a unique ability to understand developers, leveraging a rich technical background.
- Analytical Abilities: Strong background in data analysis, competitor benchmarking, and strategic planning.

EDUCATION

National University of 'Kyiv Mohyla Academy',

Bachelor's degree in **Computer Science** at one of the best universities in Ukraine. During my studies, I published several scientific articles, participated in conferences, and the examination of scientific works and writings

Mykhailo Ostrohradskyi National University,

Master's degree in Computer Science